http://www.delmarvacouncil.com/privacy-policy/64969

Council Calendar
Operating Committee Members (Program)
Wood Badge
National Youth Leader Training (NYLT)
COVID-19 Update
Privacy PolicyThe Del-Mar-Va Council website is designed to make it easier and more efficient for Council Scouters, Volunteers and the community to interact with the BSA. As with all online resources, we appreciate that many visitors to websites are concerned about their privacy. The Del-Mar-Va Council, BSA is committed to preserving your privacy when you visit our site.This policy addresses the collection, security and access to information that may be obtained through the use of websites maintained by the Del-Mar-Va Council, BSA. This policy covers the following topics: Information We Collect Public Disclosure Access Choice Cookies Security Linking Information Disclaimer Information CollectedInformation We CollectIf you visit a website maintained by the Del-Mar-Va Council, BSA to read or download information, we do not collect information about you. You should be aware that the IP server that services our domain name does collect certain information. Please visit the IP server home page for details of the server Privacy Policy.If, during your visit to the Del-Mar-Va Council, BSA website, you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information, we may collect such information. Examples of personally identifiable information may include: An email address if you are communicating to us through email. Information you voluntarily submit to the Council for the purposes of completing or submitting an application or form online. Other information volunteered, such as survey information or content of email.In general, please note the information collected, whether or not personally identifiable, is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video and other graphic formats you send us. Information is retained in accordance with existing laws and other Council policies.Public DisclosureAs a general rule, the Council does not disclose any personally identifiable information collected online except where you have given us permission, or where the information is public information. Visitors should be aware that information collected by the Council on its websites may be subject to examination and inspection, if such information is a public record and not otherwise protected from disclosure.AccessAny personally identifiable information you enter in a user profile will be open and accessible to you for review and modification. If you have any questions or comments about the information presented in this Privacy Policy, you can contact the Council Office at info@delmarvacouncil.orgChoiceYou may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e., surveys or emails). Your choice to not participate will have no effect on your ability to access information on the Council's website.CookiesWe do not use "cookies" to customize your browsing experience. Cookies are simple text files stored by your web browser and they provide a method of distinguishing among visitors to the web sites. If you have further questions about cookies, the Computer Incident Advisory Capacity Unit that monitors computer problems for the U.S. Department of Energy issued a study on March 12, 1998, of the risks to users of cookies, titled "Information Bulletin 1-034: Internet Cookies."SecurityIn certain instances, you will have the opportunity to receive or create a password to access or submit personal information. You should not divulge your password to anyone and the Council will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. When you are finished with those applications that are password protected, you should exit the page.Information DisclaimerInformation provided on the Council's website is intended to allow the public immediate access to public information. While all attempts are made to provide accurate, current and reliable information we recognize the possibility of human and/or mechanical error. Therefore, the Del-Mar-Va Council, its board, employees, officers and agencies expressly deny any warranty of the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published by this system and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance upon the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Any person who relies upon such information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.
Contact
Program Partners
Locations
Website Privacy Policy
© 2017 Del-Mar-Va Council,
Boy Scouts of America - All Rights Reserved
Twitter
Facebook
